https://www.comforcehealth.com/ca-consumer-privacy-act-policy/

CA Consumer Privacy Act PolicyIntroductionThe California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) was enacted in 2018 and takes effect on January 1, 2020. It confers new privacy rights for consumers and imposes corresponding obligations on businesses subject to it.ACS Solutions is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy for California residents (“Policy”) applies to personal information collected through our websites, applications, services, and in the course of routine offline business contact with you. It applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California (“consumers,” “your,” or “you”).This Policy has been adopted to comply with the CCPA and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Policy.The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to ACS Solutions and its affiliates (the “Company”). What Personal Information Do We Collect?For purposes of this Policy, “Personal Information” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with California consumers.We may collect Personal Information from you in a variety of different situations, including, but not limited to, through our websites, your mobile device, through email, in physical locations, through the mail, and/or over the telephone.We collect Personal Information to operate, manage, and maintain our business, to provide our services, and to accomplish our business purposes and objectives. In particular, we may have collected the following categories of Personal Information from consumers within the last twelve (12) months:Identifiers, such as names and government-issued identifiers (e.g., Social Security numbers);Personal Information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute, such as contact information and financial information;Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as sex;Biometric information, such as fingerprints and voiceprints;Internet or network activity information, such as browsing history and interactions with our websites;Geolocation data, such as device location and Internet Protocol (IP) location;Audio, electronic, and similar information, such as call and video recordings;Professional or employment-related information, such as work history and prior employers;Education information, such as student records, grades, and transcripts; andInferences drawn from any of the Personal Information listed above to create a profile about, for example, an individual’s preferences and characteristics.Personal Information does not include:Publicly available information from government records;De-identified or aggregated consumer information;Information excluded from the CCPA’s scope, such as: health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 2009 (HIPAA), the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA), or clinical trial data; personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA), or the California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA); and the Driver’s Privacy Protection Act of 1994.The categories of sources from which we collected the Personal Information listed above include, but are not limited to:Directly from job candidates/applicants and employees; For example, when theyContact the Company by phone, email, or otherwise in respect of any of its services;Apply for assignments that the Company has advertised on behalf of its clients or itself; andComplete contract assignments at client sites, including logs of work completed and hours worked.Sources such as LinkedIn, corporate websites, job board websites, online CV libraries, business cards, personal recommendations, and the Company’s websites;Service providers, including external payroll service providers, and other third parties;Directly from clients, contractors, or their agents.For example, from information clients provide in relation to the services for which they engage the Company.How Do We Use Personal Information?We may use or disclose the Personal Information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:Job Candidate/Applicant Information – We generally use the Personal Information about job candidates/applicants in the following ways:a) Recruitment Services – Because a significant area of our business is providing recruitment services, we have listed below various ways in which we may use and process Personal Information for this purpose, when appropriate and in accordance with any legal requirements. This list is not exhaustive.Collecting the information from job candidates/applicants and other sources, such as LinkedIn;Storing the information (and updating it when necessary) in our databases, so that we can contact job candidates/applicants in relation to recruitment;Providing job candidates/applicants with our recruitment services and to facilitate the recruitment process;Assessing information about job candidates/applicants to compare it against vacancies that we think might be suitable for them;Sending job candidates’/applicants’ information to clients, to apply for assignments or to assess their eligibility for assignments;Enabling job candidates/applicants to submit their CVs, apply online for jobs, or subscribe to alerts about jobs that might be of interest to them;Carrying out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between the Company and job candidates/applicants;Carrying out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between the Company and third parties in relation to job candidates’/applicants’ recruitment;Facilitating our payroll and invoicing processes;Verifying the details that job candidates/applicants have provided, using third party resources or by requesting additional information;Complying with our legal obligations in connection with the detection of crime or the collection of taxes or duties; andProcessing job candidates’/applicants’ information to enable us to send them targeted, relevant marketing materials or other communications which we think are likely to be of interest to them.b) Marketing Activities – We may use Personal Information for the purposes listed below, when appropriate and in accordance with any legal requirements. This list is not exhaustive.Enabling us to develop and market other services; andMarketing our full range of recruitment services (permanent, temporary, contract, Managed Service Provider programs, etc.) to job candidates/applicants.c) We may use Personal Information to help us comply with legal or regulatory requirements for job candidates/applicants, including government reporting, investigations, legal proceedings, record-keeping, and for audit purposes. Employee Information – We use the Personal Information of our employees for remuneration, taxation, pension, and benefits purposes. The information requested is necessary for the performance of our obligations under their employment contracts. If employees do not provide the information requested, we will be unable to pay them their wages, provide or register them for benefits, or facilitate claims for benefits. We may also process the Personal Information as part of performance review processes and in relation to compensation, rewards, and benefits. We also keep employee training records. We may also need to process Personal Information in connection with disciplinary, grievance, and dismissal processes. Additionally, we may use the Personal Information to help us comply with legal or regulatory requirements for employees, including government reporting, investigations, legal proceedings, record-keeping, and for audit purposes.Contractor Information– We may use the Personal Information about our contractors to:Store (and update when necessary) their details on our databases, so that we can contact them in relation to our agreements;Offer services to them or obtain support and services from them;Perform certain legal obligations; andHelp us to establish, exercise, or defend legal claims.We may also use Personal Information to facilitate administrative functions, information technology operations, for legal reasons, and corporate transactions. These functions include, but are not limited to the following:To manage and operate information technology and communications systems, risk management and insurance functions, budgeting, financial management and reporting, and strategic planning;To manage litigation and other legal matters and inquiries, and to meet legal and regulatory requirements;In connection with corporate transactions, sales, or assignments of assets; and mergers, divestitures, or other changes of control or of financial status of the Company or its subsidiaries or affiliates; andTo manage licenses, permits, and authorizations applicable to our business operations.With Whom Do We Share Personal Information?When appropriate and in accordance with legal requirements, we may share Personal Information in various ways and for various reasons, including, but not limited to:Any of our group of companies;Individuals and organizations who hold information related to job candidates’/applicants’ references or applications to work with us, such as current, past or prospective employers, educators, examining bodies, and employment and recruitment agencies;Tax, audit, or other authorities, when we believe in good faith that the law or a regulation requires us to share this information;Third party service providers who perform functions on our behalf;Third party outsourced payroll providers when we have an appropriate processing agreement (or similar protections) in place;For job candidates/applicants:Potential employers and other recruitment agencies/organizations to increase the candidates’/applicants’ chances of finding employment;Third party partners, job boards, and job aggregators when we consider this will improve the chances of finding them the right job.Managed Service Provider (MSP) suppliers as part of our clients’ MSP programs; andVendor Management System (VMS) suppliers as part of workorder tracking, time capturing services for our clients.What are your CCPA Rights?The CCPA provides certain consumers with specific rights regarding their Personal Information which they may exercise independently or through an authorized agent. It also includes several exemptions, however. For example, Personal Information about consumers who are current or former employees, job applicants, or contractors is generally exempt from, or outside the scope of, this section.The consumers who have these rights under the CCPA may exercise them in the following manner:Right to Access Information Consumers with these rights under the CCPA may request access to the Personal Information that we have collected and maintained about them (along with information regarding its use and disclosure) over the past twelve (12) months upon appropriate verification. They may make such requests two (2) times every twelve (12) months.Right to Deletion of Information Consumers with these rights under the CCPA may request that we delete Personal Information collected and maintained about them, subject to certain exceptions. Once their request is verified and we have determined that we are required to delete that information in accordance with applicable law, we will delete their Personal Information accordingly. Any deletion request may be denied if it is necessary for us to retain the information under one or more of the exceptions listed in the CCPA, such as complying with a legal obligation. Please note that a record of the deletion request may be kept pursuant to our legal obligations.Right to Non-Discrimination We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights under the CCPA.How to Make Requests?Consumers who have access and deletion rights under the CCPA may exercise these rights by submitting a verifiable consumer request using one of the methods described below.Email us at dataprivacy@acsicorp.com.Make the subject line of your email “CCPA Information/Deletion Request.”Include your first and last name.Identify which type of request you are seeking by including one of the following sentences in your email:This is a request to know categories of my Personal Information; orThis is a request to know specific pieces of my Personal Information; orThis is a request to delete my Personal Information.Include this declaration: “I affirm that the information provided in this email is accurate, that I am the person whose full name is specified above, and that I am the owner of this email account and a California resident. I understand that the Company will contact me at the email address provided to verify I am the person making this request.”Make a request through ACS Solutions Employee Hotline by:Calling (888) 585-3877 and indicating you have a CCPA Request; orVisiting www.acsicorp.com/speak-up and submitting a CCPA Request through the webform.Authorized AgentYou can designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf if:The authorized agent is a natural person or a business entity registered with the Secretary of State of California; andYou sign a written declaration that you authorize the authorized agent tot act on your behalf.An authorized agent may submit a CCPA rights request along with a copy of the written declaration, by mail to:Attention: Privacy OfficerACS Solutions 2400 Meadowbrook Parkway Duluth, GA 30096We reserve the right to deny requests from an authorized agent in certain circumstances, such as where we have a reasonable belief that the request is fraudulent.Verifying Your RequestTo help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take appropriate steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your Personal Information or complying with your request. Once we receive your request, we may verify it by requesting information sufficient to confirm your identity. The information that we ask you to provide will depend on your prior interactions with us and the sensitivity of the Personal Information at issue.Please follow the instructions above and promptly respond to any follow-up questions. If, in our sole determination in accordance with the CCPA, we are unable to verify your identity, the Company may deny the request in whole or in part.Changes to this PolicyThe Company reserves the right to update or amend this Policy at any time. A new Policy will be issued when we make significant updates or amendments.How to Contact Us?Any questions or comments about this Policy can be sent to the e-mail address dataprivacy@acsicorp.com or mailed to:Privacy Officer ACS Solutions 2400 Meadowbrook Parkway Duluth, GA 30096Last Updated: January 1, 2020Kelly Walton RHIT, CCSDirector of Healthcare ServicesKelly Walton is the Director of Healthcare Services at ComforceHealth. Kelly is a multi-credentialed coding, revenue integrity auditing and education professional with nearly 10 years of experience.Kelly’s notable experience includes developing customized coding and physician education for healthcare systems nationwide and being a 3M 360 implementation subject matter expert. Kelly is also a seasoned speaker at local and state conferences, such as MEHIMA and AAPC Bangor, ME Chapter. For several terms, Kelly taught the coding curriculum as Adjunct Faculty Member at Beal College in Bangor, ME; her alma mater. Her passion for mentoring and educating the HIM community continues in her role at ComforceHealth. Kelly’s operating motto is “steel sharpens steel and we all stand to learn from each other.”Kelly’s strong subject matter background began as an inpatient coder and since then has expanded to include professional billing, charge reconciliation, physician education and outpatient workflows. In addition, she has served as a valued member of ICD 10 implementation and revenue cycle committees.A passionate HIM professional, Kelly is proud of her professional and academic accomplishments. Kelly holds an Associates of Applied Science degree in Health Information Management and holds the AHIMA RHIT and CCS credentials. X Josh HollandVice PresidentAs the Vice President for ComforceHealth, Josh has responsibility for new client acquisition, client services and delivery. Josh joined the ComforceHealth team with a proven track record of building high performing sales and recruitment teams, leveraging his 10+ years of industry experience. He and his team are responsible for unlocking new opportunities for partnerships by driving up-sell and cross-sell initiatives and facilitating collaboration to develop impactful solutions.Driven by passion, Josh enjoys “geeking out” over helping formulate solutions with clients, never shying away from an opportunity to incorporate humor and establishing deeper connections with those he serves.Josh and his family live in Tampa, FL. During his free time, he can usually be found exploring the outdoors enjoying boating, fishing and camping. X Christina Perkins, RN, CCDSSenior Clinical Documentation Improvement Services ConsultantChristina Perkins is a Senior Clinical Documentation Improvement Services Consultant at ComforceHealth. She is a dedicated revenue cycle professional with over 11 years of experience. During her career, Christina has had the unique opportunity to travel across the country as a senior consultant, curating her skills to include analyzing, implementing, and improving CDI departments at various healthcare facilities. Christina has experience across a wide range of facility types, from large teaching hospitals and university health systems to a multi-hospital heath system with critical access and community net facilities. She has significant experience in developing CDI departments from the ground up and re-vamping previously established departments to assess opportunities for clinical and financial improvements in DRG, SOI, and ROM.Christina is also an expert in denials management, recovery audit review and appeals. She has successfully implemented and managed denials management teams and processes with exceptional results.Prior to joining ComforceHealth, Christina flourished as a revenue cycle and coding leader by significantly improving DNFB totals and denial overturn rates. Christina has successfully engaged and earned the trust of healthcare professionals across the revenue cycle spectrum, including clinicians.Christina’s experience allows her to offer wholistic, expert guidance with respect to the revenue cycle while understanding the unique challenges down to the facility level. Christina is passionate about continuing education and is a proud CDI professional. X Joe AndrewsDirector of RecruitmentJoe Andrews is the Director of Recruitment and is responsible for the performance management of ComforceHealth’s national recruitment team. In this role, he leads the development and execution of comprehensive recruiting strategies that will guarantee that the business attracts and hires the top talent in the industry.He and his team work strategically with the business development and client services teams to ensure we deliver the right match to our clients in 48 hours or less.Joe has over 15 years of total staffing experience, with the last 10 being dedicated to revenue integrity. Joe started out as a recruiter and because of his success as an individual contributor, worked his way up to Director. Under his leadership, he has coached and mentored several to becoming company Top Performers.Joe earned a Bachelor of Science at Greensboro College in Greensboro North Carolina and he is currently an active member of the Pinellas County Foster and Adoption association. X Jeanette Thomas, RHIA, CCS, COC, CPC AHIMA Approved ICD10CM & PCS TrainerCoding Operations ManagerAs a
Coding Operations Manager for ComforceHealth, Jeanette is responsible for the management and delivery of coding services for an assigned group of coding consultants and clients. Jeanette monitors coder productivity, quality , and all areas of consultant accountability to ensure the success of the business.She interacts directly with the client, ensuring the success and growth of the project and collaborates with all areas of ComforceHealth to ensure successful and profitable client engagement.Jeanette Thomas is an accomplished healthcare industry leader with 20 years of experience. Her background in Health Information Management includes clinical, facility, auditing, DRG Validation, educational services and management. She has also worked several years with the Revenue Cycle as a Manager of Patient Financial Services and Managing Quality and Training for the Revenue Cycle.She has been an educator for 15 years, teaching in HIM programs as an Adjunct instructor for the RHIT Associate Degree program for CAHIM approved education institutes and the CCS certificate program.Jeanette earned her Associates of Applied Science in HIM and her Bachelor of Science in Technical Management /Healthcare Administration from DeVry University.She has served on committees with AAPC as Education Chair, GAHIMA as Membership Chair and Healthcare Financial Management Association on the Certified Patient Account Rep (CPAR) committee. X Donna Sherburne, RHIT, CCS, CCS-PDirector of Coding OperationsDonna Sherburne is the Director of Coding Operations here at ComforceHealth. In this role, she leads the Coding Department for the organization’s domestic and global workforce. Collaborating with our Global and Domestic leaders, she oversees the execution of meeting our clients coding needs by managing best practices while maintaining compliance, integrity, quality, and providing proven results.Donna is a known industry leader and has over 17 years of Health Information Management (HIM) experience in facility and profee coding, including both inpatient and outpatient services. She focuses on providing our clients with solution-driven results by Managing Coding Volumes revenue cycle initiatives/issues including DNFB/DNFC, Coding Denials provides the coding team with her subject matter extensive experience in MS-DRGs, APR-DRGs, DRG Validation, ICD 10 CM/PCS and CPT code assignment, auditing, education and clinical documentation improvement (CDI). She has proven abilities to manage complex workloads and project management skill set.Donna earned her Associates of Applied Science in HIM from Joliet Junior College, IL, where she graduated Magna Cum Laude. Prior to joining ComforceHealth, her continued passion for coding afforded her the opportunity to serve in various Managing roles leveraging her expertise to mentor new coders while identifying process improvement opportunities and partnering with executive teams to optimize operations and overall service delivery. X Melissa JohnsonGroup Vice President of ComforceHealthAs the Group Vice President for ComforceHealth, Melissa has ultimate responsibility for all operations for the organization. She also sets the strategic vision and direction for ComforceHealth, working towards achieving financial goals and objectives, and increasing operating performance.Melissa has 12 years of dedicated experience serving middle revenue cycle. She is a results driven leader with a proven track record of exceeding revenue and bottom-line goals.Prior to joining the ComforceHealth team, Melissa was the Vice President of Strategic Business Development at himagine solutions where her responsibilities included securing major new business and developing large, high-profile strategic accounts. Before himagine solutions, Melissa was a Regional Sales Vice President, Southeast, at Precyse.Melissa holds a BA in Psychology from the University of South Florida and is a member of FHIMA, AHIMA, and HFMA.Melissa JohnsonGroup Vice President( O ): 813.349.1771 ( C ): 813.464.5710 X ComforceHealth uses cookies to improve the functionality, performance, and effectiveness of our communications. For more information on our data policies, please visit our privacy policy. By continuing to use this site, or by clicking "I agree," you consent to the use of cookies. Privacy Preferences. I Agree
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies Powered by  GDPR Cookie Compliance Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful. Strictly Necessary CookiesStrictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings. disable
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again. Enable All Save Settings
Contact Us
